﻿[Script Info]
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 2
PlayResX: 1000
PlayResY: 320
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 0
Video Position: 0
Collisions: Normal
[V4+ Styles]
Style: Default,方正大标宋_GBK,54,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00295479,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0,1,2,0,5,10,10,10,1
[Events]
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs25\blur3\pos(800,250)}白学家

